L:I don't wanna let the chance slip away
不願讓機會溜掉
Why is my freedom taken away?
為什麼會被剝奪自由
reason as against emotion
與感性相對比的理性
l've gotta deal with extreme frustration
不得不克服失望感
E:All my efforts will never be in vain
所有努力決不會白費
Endless desire,like a haunting refrain
就像沒有終點的慾望翻覆於心中
D:Such a pain,the ideal versus the real
理想與現實之間的痛苦
L:There is a way E:To change the world
應該有改變時間的方法的
D:Just count on me
對 就這麼交給我吧
L:So what if I sing off-key,who cares
不固定音程去唱歌 也沒什麼大不了的
Not good at drawing,no big deal
糟糕的繪畫也無所謂
E:Let me go for my one true belief
我為了唯一的信念而前進
E:Overcome myself
L:Overcome yourself
我要勝過我自己
你要勝過你自己
D:"A Ahole New World God Only Knows"
"只有神知道的全新世界"
E:I'll always be on your side
我一直都是你的夥伴
L:I know you're hurting inside
我知道你在痛苦著
E:To be a knight D:To be a light L:For you
成為騎士,成為照耀你的明燈
E:We'll be shining bright
我們會就這樣閃耀下去
L:No more fears D:No more tears
已經不再恐懼 不再流淚
Everything will work out
一切都會順利的
That's "God only knows"
這便是"只有神知道"
E:Don't get me wrong
別誤會了
This is not real love but
這不是現實中的戀愛 但是
D:I'll do anything for you
為了你 我願意做任何事情
L:Whatever happens in my life,turn the page and come of age
無論我的生命中發生什麼事 都會翻過嶄新的一頁長大成人
E:Remember,no one can judge me
不要忘記 我不想被任何人所評說
L:Every end leads to a new beginning of rhe next stage
一切的終結都通往著下一個舞台的開始
E:Try to make my life complete,trust myself
理解走過的人生 相信自己
D:Be strong and do my best
變得更強 做到最好
Don't look back,carry on
不回首過去 持續前進
C:Be yourself... Be happy... It's your life...
活出你自己的幸福... 因為這是你自己的人生
"God only knows"
"只有神知道"
Find your love... Find your way... For your life...
找到愛... 找到道路... 為了你自己的人生